nellyfurtado.com 2019-07-07

# 

### NELLY FURTADO  
PRIVACY NOTICE

Nelstar Entertainment, Inc. (“Nelstar”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Notice. This Privacy Notice lets you know how and for what purposes we are collecting, processing, and using your Personal Information (as defined herein). We pledge that we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information will only be used in ways that are in compliance with this Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice is in effect for any web page, mobile application, third party social media site, email list, onsite electronic data collection, generic information, and Personal Information (as defined herein) collected and/or owned by us, including but not limited to the Nelly Furtado official website, located at www.nellyfurtado.com (the “Nelly Furtado Site”), no matter the method of collection (e.g., mail, facsimile, sign-up/sign-in page, survey, promotion), including collection through the Nelly Furtado Site and any online features, services, and/or programs we offer (collectively, the “Web Properties”). Notwithstanding the foregoing, this Privacy Notice is not applicable to any other web page, mobile application, social media site, generic information, or Personal Information collected and/or owned by any entity other than Nelstar or one of its parents, affiliates and/or subsidiaries.

This Privacy Notice also applies to information collected by or for us through a means other than the Web Properties. If the same information is collected through the Web Properties and through a means other than the Web Properties, the terms of this Privacy Notice shall apply.

Your use of the Web Properties is also governed by the Terms of Use.

#### Types of Information Collected

Nelstar and any third party we engage for the purpose of administering, operating, hosting, configuring, designing, maintaining and providing internal support for our Web Properties, may collect two types of information when you visit the Web Properties: personal information and usage information.

**Personal Information:** In order to participate in certain features, services and/or programs of the Web Properties, we may require that you provide us with certain specific information, which we may collect including, among other similar types of information (collectively, “Personal Information”): (1) contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number, email address); (2) demographic information (e.g., date of birth); (3) bank account and credit/debit card numbers; and (4) your physical location.

**Usage Information:** We may obtain non-individualized, generic information about you when you visit the Web Properties. This may include your (i) Internet Protocol (or IP) address, protocol and sequence information; browser language; browser type; domain name system requests; browsing history (including time spent at a domain, time and date of your visit); number of clicks; hypertext transfer protocol headers; application client and server banners; and operating system fingerprinting data (collectively, “Usage Information”); and (ii) MAC address, device ID/UDID, or similar device-specific code used for advertising/marketing tracking purposes.

#### How Information Is Collected

We may collect Personal Information and Usage Information about you from the following sources:

  * information we receive from you, or on your behalf, through forms you complete, or if you contact us, for example to raise a query, to sign up for our mailing list, or to sign up to receive notifications when Nelly Furtado is on tour near you;
  * information we receive from you through the Web Properties, such as when creating an account, placing an order or joining our mailing list;
  * information we receive from your computer or mobile device;
  * information we receive from our partners or service providers; and
  * information we receive from other sources, as permitted by applicable laws, rules and regulations.

We may sponsor promotions through the Web Properties. Your participation is entirely voluntary. You may be asked to provide personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name or email address, or to answer questions in order to participate. We may also transfer Personal Information to certain advertising or marketing partners from whom you have requested to receive information.

#### Additional Ways that Information is Collected Through the Web Properties

We may collect Usage Information from you as follows:

**Browser Log Files:** Our servers automatically log each visitor to the Web Properties and collect and record certain Usage Information about each visitor. The Usage Information reveals nothing personal about the user and includes only the generic information described in the definition of “Usage Information.” We may use this information to examine our traffic in the aggregate, but we do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals.

**Cookies:** From time to time, we and/or our advertisers or other third parties may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive and that can be re-sent to the serving website on subsequent visits. A cookie, by itself, cannot read other data from your hard disk or read other cookie files already on your computer. A cookie, by itself, does not damage your system. We, our advertisers and other third parties may use cookies to identify and keep track of, among other things, those areas of the Web Properties and third party websites that you have visited in the past in order to enhance your next visit to the Web Properties. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times that you have seen an advertisement and obtain similar analytical information. You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser, but some functionality of the Web Properties may be impaired or not function as intended if you choose not to accept cookies.

**Web Beacons:** Some of our web pages and electronic communications may contain images, which may or may not be visible to you, known as Web Beacons (sometimes referred to as ‘clear gifs’). Web Beacons collect only limited information that includes a cookie number; time and date of a page view; and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. We may also carry Web Beacons placed by third party advertisers. These Web Beacons do not carry any Personal Information and are only used to track usage of the Web Properties and activities associated with the Web Properties.

**Unique Identifier:** We may assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we use it to personalize the information you see on the Web Properties and some of the electronic communications you receive from us. We keep this information for our internal use, and this information is not shared with others.

#### Use of Personal Information

The Personal Information that we collect may be used for three main purposes:

  1. To enable the features of the Web Properties, including, but not limited to: (a) operating any promotions in which you may participate; (b) setting up and managing your online account, including, but not limited to, our processing your requests for information about Nelly Furtado or performances near you; and/or (c) providing products or services to you.
  2. To improve the Web Properties by determining which of our products, features and services are most popular. We may analyze your information and browsing information to enable us and our affiliates to provide services to you and develop new features, functionality, and services and otherwise for our internal business purposes.
  3. To communicate with you and to inform you about our and third parties’ products and services. We and/or any of our third party service providers may send you and keep you updated with information about existing and new services, products, and special offers, by email, telephone, mail or by means of any other contact details you provide to us or our affiliates, or to such third party service providers.

#### When Information Is Disclosed

We might disclose Personal Information and/or Usage Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with legal processes and applicable law; (2) enforce this Privacy Notice; (3) take precautions against liability and to respond to any claim that any material, document, image, graphic, logo, design, audio, video, audio-visual material, photos, commentary and any other information provided to, from or on the Web Properties by you violates the rights of third parties; (4) assist government enforcement agencies; or (5) protect our rights, property, or the safety or the rights, property, or personal safety of our visitors and the public.

We use reasonable precautions to keep the information that is disclosed to us secure. We may provide Personal Information and Usage Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and other businesses or persons for the purposes of processing such information on our behalf and promoting the goods and services of our trusted business partners, some or all of which may store some or all of your information on servers outside of the United States. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Notice or in a similar, industry-standard manner, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use appropriate confidentiality and security measures. The use of your information by one of our trusted business partners may be subject to that party’s own privacy notice.

We may share Usage Information with third parties to demonstrate the usage patterns for advertisements, content, functionality, promotions, and/or services on the Web Properties and/or on third party websites.

We reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information, as well as any information about or from you, in connection with the merger, sale or other disposition of all or part of our business and/or assets. We cannot make any representations regarding the use or transfer of your Personal Information or other information that we may have in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership, or an assignment for the benefit of creditors, and you expressly agree and consent to the use and/or transfer of your Personal Information or other information in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in any of the above described proceedings. Furthermore, we cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third parties or for any actions of any third parties that receive any of the information that is disclosed to us.

We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission.

#### Information from Children

We do not collect Personal Information from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13). Specifically, the Web Properties are not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13). You will need to affirm that you are more than eighteen (18) years of age, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this Privacy Notice, and to abide by and comply with this Privacy Notice. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of thirteen (13), as **THE WEB PROPERTIES ARE NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER THIRTEEN (13) WHO ARE UNACCOMPANIED BY THEIR PARENT(S) OR LEGAL GUARDIAN(S).**

Parents and legal guardians should be aware that this Privacy Notice will govern our use of Personal Information, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in email exchanges, bulletin boards or the like, may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. We encourage all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

#### Privacy Outside the Web Properties

The Web Properties may now or in the future contain links to other websites, including, but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, iTunes, Spotify, Amazon, YouTube and Instagram, and contain advertisements of third parties. We are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those websites. Other than under agreements with certain reputable organizations and companies, and except for third party service providers (as described in this Privacy Notice), we do not share any of the Personal Information that you provide to us with any of the websites to which the Web Properties links, although we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with those other third parties. Please check with those websites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

#### Social Features

Certain functionality on the Web Properties is specifically designed to permit interactions that you initiate between the Web Properties and third party websites or services, including third party social networks (“Social Features”). Examples of Social Features include enabling you to transmit content to the Web Properties from your account on a third party website or service, and to “like” or “share” our content on the Web Properties to other websites or services.

If you choose to use Social Features, information you post or provide access to may be publicly displayed on the Web Properties or by the provider of the Social Feature that you use. Similarly, if you post information on a third party platform that references Nelly Furtado or Nelstar (e.g., by using a hashtag associated with Nelly Furtado in a tweet or status update), your post may be published on the Web Properties in accordance with the terms of the third party website or service. Also, both Nelstar and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Web Properties and the third party site or service. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections,” or information about you is otherwise accessible through your “connections” web pages, profile pages, or similar pages on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service.

The information we collect in connection with Social Features is subject to this Privacy Notice. The information collected and stored by the third parties remains subject to those third parties’ privacy practices, including whether the third parties continue to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on those third party websites or services.

#### European Union Users

If you are visiting us from the European Union, please note that we may collect, transfer, and continue to use your Personal Information outside the European Union for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. By using the Web Properties and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our collection, transfer, and continued use of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

#### Information Security

We take reasonable efforts to ensure that information collected through the Web Properties is not lost, misused or altered inappropriately by administering security measures. However, all information accessible and/or transferred over the Internet can potentially be accessed by unauthorized parties; therefore, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Web Properties.

#### Choices with Your Personal Information

Whether you submit any Personal Information to us is entirely up to you. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information. However, this information is essential for the provision and quality of some of the services we offer to you, so we cannot provide you with certain services if you choose to withhold requested information.

You may choose to prevent us from disclosing or using your Personal Information under certain circumstances (“opt out”). You may opt out of any disclosure or use of your Personal Information for purposes that are incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for which you subsequently gave authorization by notifying us by one of the methods at the end of this Privacy Notice, or by following the procedures set forth in an electronic communication from us, if applicable. Furthermore, even where your Personal Information is to be disclosed and used in accordance with the stated purposes in this Privacy Notice, you may elect to opt out of such disclosure to and use by a third party that is not acting as our agent. There are some uses from which you cannot opt out, such as to provide products or services that you have requested from us.

#### Access and Correction

Please contact us in the manner specified at the end of this Privacy Notice to access your Personal Information in our possession and correct inaccuracies of that information in our records. We ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed and amended before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests in limited circumstances, as permitted by applicable privacy legislation.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide certain personally identifiable information in connection with obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us (once a calendar year) information about the customer information we shared (if any) with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2017 will receive information regarding 2016 sharing activities, if any).

To obtain this information, please send an email message to info@10thst.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your email address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements, and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

#### “Do Not Track” Signals

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, Nelstar currently does not alter its practices when it receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit www.allaboutdnt.com.

#### Your Consent to This Privacy Notice

By using the Web Properties, you consent to the collection and use of your information (including Personal Information) by us as specified above or as we otherwise see fit, in compliance with this Privacy Notice, unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below. If we decide to change this Privacy Notice or some part of it, we will make an effort to post those changes on this web page so that you will always be able to understand what information we collect, how we use that information and under what circumstances we may disclose that information to others. Your use of the Web Properties following such publication of any amendment of this Privacy Notice will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms for all previously collected information and information collected from you in the future. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

If you have additional questions or comments or would like to access your recorded Personal Information or opt out of certain sharing, please let us know by sending your comments or requests to:

Nelstar Entertainment Inc.  
c/o 10th Street Entertainment  
6420 Wilshire Blvd., #950  
Los Angeles, CA 90048  
Phone: 310-385-4700  
info@10thst.com.com

Copyright © 2017. Nelstar Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.  
Effective as of: January 27, 2017  
Last updated: January 27, 2017
